Previously on Desperate Housewives
前情提要
My husband died thinking that I murdered him
我的丈夫临死之前认为是我害死了他
Bree put the past behind her
(Bree终于跟往事作别）
If you keep me on as your lawyer your wife's off limlits
只要我做你的律师 我就不会碰你的妻子
He is my lawyer While Carlos gambled with his future
(Carlos拿未来作赌注）
How much money do you think you need to get to Utah
你到犹他州需要多少钱
Susan interfere with the family reunion
(而Susan干扰了一场骨肉团聚）
George Willams had never been lucky in love
(George William情场上从没交过好运)
It seemed that the women he dated always invented reason not to consume their relationship
(似乎总会编造些原因中止两人的关系)
Oh I am afraid we may wake my roommates
恐怕我们会吵醒我的室友的
I have to get up really early for work
我明天上班得起的特别早
I am saving myself for marriage
我想我最好把我的初夜留到... 新婚之夜
Sadly for George It was one unoriginal excuse after another
(可怜的George) (得到的只是一个接一个没有创意的借口）
But since he start seeing Bree Van de Camp
(但自从他和Bree Van de Camp交往以来）
George couldn't help but feel
(George不自觉地感到...)
Hi kids has gone we have the house all to ourself tonight
嗨 孩子们都不在家 今晚家里只有我们俩
his lucky is about to change
(他终于要时来运转了）
I thought the duck turn out well although the sauce is a little bit fit
我的鸭子似乎做得不错
But judging by how many helps you had I think I get well with it
虽然酱有点稠 但考虑到没人给我打下手
What are you thinking about?
- 你在想什么呢
Your hair
- 你的秀发
Would you mind if I...
你介意我...
Oh! no go ahead
不 不介意
That's better
这样好点么？
That was nice
真好
It's OK that I am doing this, right?
- 我这样没什么不妥吧
I thought we would let the duck a bit more... but what the heck!
- 我以为我们还要多聊会鸭子
What's wrong?
怎么了
I don't know I feel something weird
不知道 我感觉很奇怪 哦 是我的舌头 我舌头比一般人伸得远 我应该提前告诉你的
Oh that's my tongue its stretch farther than most I should warned you
哦 是我的舌头 我舌头比一般人伸得远 我应该提前告诉你的
no no no it wasn't your kiss I feel something weird around my neck
不不 不是吻 我是觉得我脖子有些不对劲
What are you doing?
- 你干什么呢
I don't know I am just really starting itch
- 不知道 我就觉得好痒
What is it? You got a huge rash
你起了斑了
It's sarting * my face
开始往脸上长了
Are you allergic to something you eat?
你吃了什么过敏的东西了么
I don't think so I mean I ate duck * a thousand times
不知道 那个鸭子我都作过上千次了
Something is cause of the rash
肯定是什么引起的
Bree please don't
Bree Bree 别
I am sorry George but you have to go
对不起George 你必须离开
But the kids are away
对不起George 你必须离开 但孩子都不在家 我还希望今晚我们能做爱呢
I was sort of hope that we could make love tonight
但孩子都不在家 我还希望今晚我们能做爱呢 你怎么能George 你刚让我得了麻疹！
How could you do that George You've just given me hives
你怎么能George 你刚让我得了麻疹！
Though painful to hear
(虽然听起来着实伤心）
George had to admit
(George必须承认）
at least this excuse was original
(至少这个借口...很有创意）
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=- Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园论坛 http://www.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
Sync:YTET-fisherchen -=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
欢迎光临伊甸园美剧交流站 http://sfile.ydy.com/bbs
Desperate Housewives
欲乱绝情妻 第二季 第六集
to make those dreams come true.
(等待她们的白马王子让他们美梦成真）
Aah! Oh. Watch it,susie.
啊！看着点 Susie
Mom,why don't you just go see a dressmaker?
妈 你还是去找个裁缝吧
Wait. I have the perfect idea.
等等 我有个好主意
You get in the dress and I'll pin it.
你穿上婚纱 我自己来改它
We wear the same size.
我们的身材一样
- Since when?
- 什么时候一样过？
Since forever.
一直都是阿
You have to leave,though.
你得避让一下 你不能在这
You can't stay.
You can't see susie in a wedding dress,
你不能看Susie穿婚纱 直到你们的大喜日子
not until your big day.
No,it's not a problem.
- 不 没事
I can see her in it.
我可以看她穿这件婚纱
- You can?
- 可以？
You can?
你可以？
I assume you wanna pick out your own wedding dress when we get married,right?
我想我们结婚时候 你会自己选个新婚纱的 对吧
that sounds like a proposal.
- 哦 听起来像是求婚
Did it?
- 像么？
Yeah,it did.
是阿 像
Huh. What do you know?
- 啊 是嘛
Are you planning to pop the question?
你计划突然提出那句问题么
Well,if she knows it's coming,
要是她知道我要问那句话
the question won't really pop,
就谈不上突然了不是么
now will it?
要是她知道我要问那句话 就谈不上突然了不是么
He's right,mom. I want it to be just like you do--
他说得对 妈 我希望你按你自己的方式来
you know,on your own terms,
单膝跪地
and you get down on one knee and the whole production.
然后该怎么做就怎么做
That's the plan.
- 我就是这么想的
Well,then I can wait.
- 我能等
I can wait.
我-能-等
I'm a good waiter.
等待我拿手着呢
Good.
很好
I'm just wondering if there's a ballpark of how long
我就是想知道我大概要等多久 一周 一个月 还是午饭以后
I will have to wait--
我就是想知道我大概要等多久
a week,a month,after lunch?
一周 一个月 还是午饭以后
Again,you're not waiting for the pop.
我都说了 你不能"等待"惊喜
Right,right. I'm sorry.
对 对 对不起
Oh,mom.
哦 妈
So the hives occurred right after you kissed george?
这么说麻疹就是 在你刚刚吻了George后起的
Yes.It was the strangest thing,
是的 真是奇怪透了 也非常不便
and so inconvenient.
To be honest,
说实话 我们当时正要第一次做爱呢
I think we were about to make love for the first time.
Bree,have you considered the idea that your subconscious mind
Bree 你有没有想过是你的潜意识 想要破坏你和George的良宵？
was trying to sabotage your evening with george?
I have not considered that because that's idiotic.
事实上 我没这么想过 因为这非常愚蠢
You don't think being with george made you feel a bit guilty?
你不认为 和George在一起让你觉得愧疚么
Why should I feel guilty?
- 我有什么可愧疚的
Perhaps you felt you were about to commit adultery.
- 也许你觉得自己是在通奸
Dr. Goldfine,rex is dead.
Goldfine医生 Rex已经死了
You can't cheat on a corpse.
没人能给一个死尸带绿帽子
Well,maybe that's not how you really feel deep down.
恐怕你内心深处不是这么认为的
Oh,so you think I'm crazy?
哦 这么说你觉得是我疯了？
You say you got a case of hives for no reason.
你说你毫无缘由得了麻疹
I think there is a reason,
我认为其实是有缘由的 而且可能是心理学上的
and it's probably a psychosomatic one.
You can think whatever you want,
随便你怎么认为 但实话实说 我不信潜意识那套
but to be honest,I don't believe in the subconscious.
Every time you've said "rex" in this session,
我们谈话过程中你每次提到rex
you've stroked the place where your wedding ring used to be.
你就去摸你手上以前带戒指的地方
Why did you do that?
为什么
Let's talk about monday.
我们来谈谈周一
We are re-pitching to the kamarov people.
我们要和Kamarov公司的人再协商
Lynette,you'll be on point.
- Lynett你必须到
Great. Great. No problem.
好 好 没问题
And can you do me a favor and maybe not wear the green suit?
你能帮我个忙不穿那套绿的套装么
I... wasn't planning to,
我本来也没这么打算
uh,but... why?
- 但 为什么
The fabric. It just has this quality to it,
布料问题 它的质量好像...
like you could--
能用湿布抹干净一样
I don't know--
它的质量好像...
wipe it clean with a damp cloth.
能用湿布抹干净一样
I'll just wear a different suit,then.
那我穿件别的套装好了
Great.
- 很好
Like what,you think?
- 比如哪件 你觉得
Another suit.
别的
I have other suits.
我有别的套装
And if by other suits,you mean the gray one,
如果你的"别的"是指灰色那套
then of course you do.
- 你确实是有"别的套装"
No,actually,I have quite a few others.
不 其实我还有一些别的
Uh,the blue one and,uh...
蓝色的 还有...
what's wrong with the blue suit?
蓝色套装又怎么了
Stu,would you liketo tell lynette what's wrongwith the blue suit?
Stu 你能告诉Lynette那套蓝色的怎么了么
No. That's cool.
- 没怎么 挺好
Stu... come on.
- Stu 说吧
Do the thing--
再来一次
the thing that you did at lunch.
你午餐时候做得那个
"Look at me. I'm lynette.
看看我 我是 Lynette
"I've got food stains everywhere."
我到处是食物的污渍
All right. So if I get my blue suit dry-cleaned,
好吧 那如果我把我的蓝套装干洗了 大家可以接受了么
will that be acceptableto everyone?
大家可以接受了么
The pants also have a split seam in the back.
那套裤子后面撕裂的线缝
Excuse me.
让一下
Hello,david.
你好 David
What the hell is this?
你是套什么玩艺
I thought i told you to dress maternal.
我不是让你穿的像个母亲一样么
Yes,you did,and i considered it for about a second.
是阿 我也考虑了一秒钟
What happened?
- 怎么了
David,i know you're the lawyer and all,
- david 我知道你是个律师
but trust me,it's never a smart strategy to cover this up.
但相信我 把这么好的身材盖起来可不怎么聪明
We've got 40 minutes before the pre-trial hearing.
我们在预审听证会前还有40分钟
- Let's go home and get you changed.
我们回家 给你换套衣服
What?
什么
You want to get your husband out of jail?
你想让你丈夫出狱
You gotta dress like a pregnant,suffering wife,
你就得穿得像个孕妇 黄脸婆 而不是像Vogue杂志封面一样
- not the cover of "vogue."
而不是像Vogue杂志封面一样
David.
David
- Louis,what are you doing here?
- David
I need a favor,david.
Louis 你来干什么
If this has to do with lifting my client's restraing order,
要是关于我的当事人的强制命令 我的答案还和上周一样
the answer's the same one you got last week.
You don't understand. I love crystal.
你不明白 我爱Crystal
Yeah,we all love the pretty ladies at the stop n' shop,
是阿 我们都爱Stop'N'Shop里的漂亮女士
but now you' gotta love her from 50 yards away.
但你现在得在50尺以外爱她了
You turned her against me
是你让她反抗我的 要不是你 我们会在一起的
If it wasn't for you,we'd be together.
Louis,crystal hired me to keep you away from her.
Louis  crystal雇佣我让你离她远点
She doesn't want to see you.
- 她不想见你
Oh,yeah,then why did she ask for my phone number?
- 是么 那她为什么要我的电话号码
She's a cashier.You paid by check. It doesn't make you special.
她是收银员 你是支票付款 她对谁都一样
Don't walk away from me. We're having a conversation!
别走 我跟你谈话呢
Louis,this is your problem.
Louis 这就是你的问题
You're creepy! Nobody likes you.
你让人发毛 没人喜欢你
What you call a conversation the rest of us call harassment.
你管这叫谈话 我们觉得是骚扰
You want a friend, get a hamster.
你要是需要朋友 买个荷兰鼠养
David!
David
call the police!
叫警察
stay there!
别动
That's right,you better run,
对了 最好快跑
'cause i'm gonna get some bullets for this thing and come after y!
小心我找几颗子弹放上去追你
Freeze!
别动
Hey,everything's cool.
嗨 已经没事了
Are you okay?
你没事吧
weeds are a common annoyance of life in suburbia,
(杂草是郊区最为常见的恼人之物）
and no matter how hard we try to get rid of them...
(不管你多么拚命去除掉它们）
they always tend to crop back up.
(它们总会又长出来）
A-are you seeing this?
你看见了吗
I don't believe him. He is so brazen.
他肯真行 真够厚颜无耻的
He's just mowing the lawn like nothing ever happened.
他就好像没事人一样在那修剪草坪
What should we do? Should we call the police?
我们该怎么办 应该叫警察么
Well,susan did say that he murdered mrs. Huber,so my vote would be yes.
Susan说他谋杀了Huber太太 所以我觉得应该
Oh,my god,susan's home.
哦 天哪 susan回来了
Has she seen paul yet?
她看见paul了么
I think so.
我想是的
Hello,susan.
你好 Susan
Oh,my god. Paul.
哦 天哪 paul
Need some help with those bags?
用我帮忙拿袋子么
Why... are you doing here?
你在这干什么呢
This is where i live. I came home to find my son.
这是我住的地方啊 我回家找我儿子
- Here you go.
- 给你
No,don't come near me.
别 离我远点
- I'm just giving you back your pie filling.
- 我只是还你做派用的馅
I don't want my pie filling.
我不想要做派用的馅
- oh,come on. Just take it.
- 哦行了 拿着
No,stop!
不 别动
Put that pie filling down.
把馅放下
Slowly.
慢慢的
- I'm calling 9-1-1.
- 我要打911了
You don't want to do that.
你不想的
Oh,i think i do. You're a cold-blooded murderer.
哦 我想得很 你是个冷血杀手
Susan,how can you believe that? We've been neighbors for years.
susan 你怎么相信这套呢 我们都做了这么多年邻居
Ladies,good to see you.
女士们 很高兴看到你们
Paul, we've called the police.
paul 我们已经叫了警察了
You didn't really need to do that.
你们不必如此的 我们知道你对Huber太太做了什么
We know what you did to mrs. Huber.
我们知道你对Huber太太做了什么
Wonderful. I see you've all turned into susan while i've been gone.
很好 我走了之后你们都变成susan了
Oh,thank god. They're here.
哦 感谢上帝 他们来了
Hey,what's going on?
嗨 怎么了
Oh,mayer's convinced that paul young murdered martha huber.
Mayer认为 是Paul young杀了Martha huber
Oh,my god. I live right behind him.
哦 天哪 我就住在他后面
I know. I gave him my house keys to feed my cat.
是啊 我给过他我家钥匙好帮我喂猫
I win. I made out with him.
我赢了 我和他搞过
Here you go. There's no warrant here for a paul young.
给你 我们没有paul young的逮捕令
Why don't you ask mike? He overheard everything,right?
你为什么不问Mike 他什么都听到了是吧
- Who's mike?
- mike是谁
Uh,he's my boyfriend,
阿 他是我男朋友
and he told me that paul confessed everything to him.
他告诉我paul把所有事都告诉他了
Oh,and mike has martha's journals,
而且Mike有martha的日记 上面可以证明paul有杀人动机
which clearly prove that paul had a motive.
All right,all right, where do i find this mike guy?
- 好吧 好吧 那个mike在哪
Uh,he's... follow me.
哦他...跟我来
You mind if i stay here? I've got a lot of raking to do.
你介意我就在这么 我还要耙地呢
Let's go.
走
Hey.
嗨
What's going on?
怎么了
Mike,paul young is back.
mike paul young回来了
Look.
看
Your girlfriend said mr. Young confessed a murder to you?
你的女朋友说 young先生对你承认他杀过人了？
no. No,not to me.
没 没 没对我说过
And i don't suppose you have a journal that belonged to a martha huber?
那我想你没有 属于martha huber的日记了?
No. I hardly knew her.
没有 我都不怎么认识她
Besides,you ever known a woman who'd loan out her diary?
另外 哪个女人会把日记借出去阿
Mike,what are you doing?
mike 你干什么呢
I'm sorry,susan. I don't know what you're talking about.
对不起 susan 我不知道你在说些什么
But i've got a job to get to. Is there anything else?
我有工作要做 还有别的事么
No,no, that pretty much covers it.
没了 已经足够了
Well,someone might as well say it.
有人也会禁不住要问了
Susan,what the hell have you been smoking?
susan 你吃错了什么药了
Okay.
好了
Wow!
喔！
Nice.
很棒
Oh,my god.
哦天哪
Okay,don't be distracted by that. Look at me.
好了 别为这个分散注意力 看我
Here i am tomorrow,
我明天就这样 做我的演讲
making my presentation.
You see? You see how it moves with me?
看到衣服怎么摆动了么
That's where the magic is.
这就是魔力所在
$900?
900美元？
Yeah,well,this one was the most expensive.
是阿 这是最贵的一套 其他的都没这么好
The other ones aren't as nice. But look.
是阿 这是最贵的一套 其他的都没这么好 但 看看
Look,look,look,look at me, look at me. Watch.
看 看 看 看我 看着我 看
I don't walk in it. I glide.
穿着它我不是走动 而是滑动
Um,honey,you know what?
亲爱的 这些衣服要3000多左右！
There's gotta be like $3,000 worth of clothes here.
Yeah,well,i haven't bought a new suit in six years.
是阿 我都6年没买过套装了
So? When i was working,
那怎么了, 我工作的时候 你以为我不想要件高级套装么
you don't think i would have loved to have a designer suit?
I wore wash-and-wear so that we could live in a nice neighborhood,
我穿得都是便宜货 这样我们才能住在好的社区 我们才能每年夏天带孩子们度假
so we could take the kids on vacation every summer.
这样我们才能住在好的社区 我们才能每年夏天带孩子们度假
- I mean,i made sacrifices.
- 我做出了牺牲
I'm willing to make sacrifices.
我愿意做出牺牲啊
Great,well,let's start here,because
很好 那就从现在开始 因为...
this should cover a math tutor for parker.
- 这个足够给parker找个数学家教了
- Whoa,hold on a sec.
- 噢 等等
Six months of preschool for penny.
penny半年的学前班费用!
All right, now you're being ridiculous.
好了 现在你有点荒谬了
You know what? And the twins... they're gonna need braces.
知道么？还有双胞胎 他们需要矫正牙齿
That ought a make a dent.
这件的钱够他们用了 哦 别 行了 tom 别这件也算上
Oh,no. Come on,tom. Not this one.
哦 别 行了 tom 别这件也算上
Strip.
脱了
You saw the walk,right?
你看到我走路的姿势了吧 想看我再走一次么
You wanna see the walk again?
- I'll tutor parker myself. - Honey,that'd be great.
我给parker当家教 宝贝 那可好极了 你也想充当家庭牙医
You also gonna take up home dentistry?
宝贝 那可好极了 你也想充当家庭牙医
Fine. I'll take them back.
好！ 我退了去
Could you step out for a minute,please?
你能出去一会么
I want to be alone with it for a little while.
我想要独自和它呆一会
Hi,it's bree.
嗨 我是Bree
Hi. I was thinking about calling you.
嗨 我正要给你打呢
I just got some new antihistamines in at the store.
店里来了些抗过敏的药 我想应该对你的疹子有效
I think they're really gonna help with your rash.
Well,great.
不错啊
how would you feel about the two of us checking into a romantic hotel tomorrow?
我们两个明天找一个浪漫的旅馆你觉得如何
What? Uh,l-i'd like that very much.
什么 我再高兴不过了
I will let you make all of the arrangements.
我让你来负责所有安排 在镇外的什么地方就好
Something out of town would be nice.
Good night.
晚安
- We need to talk. - Where did you come from?
- 你从哪冒出来的 不好意思 我一直在等你
I'm sorry. I've been waiting for you.
I'm just a little upset because everybody thinks i'm crazy.
我有点不高兴 因为人人都以为我疯了
Can i at least get out of the truck first?
我能先从车里出来么
Yes,definitely.
能 当然
I mean,i can understand why you wouldn't want the cops to know that you kidnapped paul.
我是说 我能理解你 为什么不想警察知道你绑架了paul
- I mean,that definitely looks bad.
- 的确会让你看起来是坏人
Since i was on probation.
我还在缓刑阶段
Well,right. I mean,there's that.
- 对...有道理
And in possession of a gun...
我还有枪
- well,okay...
- 好
which i held to his head.
我拿它指着他的脑袋
So i violated my probation, committed a felony and coerced a confession.
我违反了缓刑的规定 绑架了人 强迫对方认罪
If the cops found out about that i'd be looking at 10 to 15 years.
要是警察知道了 我就得进去10到15年了
But why don't you want 'em to know about martha huber's journal?
但你为什么不让他们知道 martha huber的日记呢
I mean,she says right in there that she was blackmailing paul's wife.
她在里面说得很清楚她在勒索paul的妻子
She also says right in there that she was blackmailing you for burning down edie's house.
她还在里面说得很清楚她在勒索你 因为你烧了edie的房子
Oh.
因为你烧了edie的房子
I forgot about that.
我都忘了
I just can't believe it.
真是难以置信
I mean,there he is, a murderer,
他就在那 一个凶手 就住在我们的街上
just living right on our street,
and there's nothing we can do about it
我们却什么也做不了 因为你有前科而我纵了火
because you're a convicted felon and i burnedown that stupid house.
It's not fair.
真不公平
I want paul young gone as badly as you do,
我和你一样想paul young消失
and he will be, but i also want to find zach.
但我也想找到zach
I think ce zach finds out paul's here,
我想他如果知道paul在这
i got a feeling he'll be back.
他应该会回来的
Well,that's comforting to know there's a silver lining.
祸种有福真是安慰多了
hi.
嗨
What are you doing here?
你在这干什么
Well,you protected me from a hail of gunre,
你在枪林弹雨中保护了我 所以我想我该来看看你
so i thought i'd stop by and give you a card.
你在枪林弹雨中保护了我 所以我想我该来看看你 送张卡片
You're my first visitor.
你是我第一个看望者
What do you mean,i'm your first visitor?You've been here two days.
什么你第一个看望者？ 你都在这呆了两天了
My office sent me flowers.
我的办公室给我送来了花
Oh. "dear david,
"亲爱的David"
"who knew you could actually bleed?
"没想到你也能流出血来"
"Sincerely, your stunned co-workers."
"你真诚 惊愕的同事们"
Yeah,well,i'm a lawyer who got shot.Everybody's cracking wise.
是啊 我是个中弹的律师 每个人都很精明
You're not gonna eat.
你不吃么？
Uh,can't really cut y.
我没法切...
Well,i'm not gonna let you starve to death.
我不能让你饥饿致死阿
Besides,you're gonna need your strength to get my husband out of jail.
另外我需要你有力气把我丈夫弄出来
You know,when i was waiting for the ambulance the other day...
知道么 那天在我等救护车的时候
i seriously thought i was gonna die.
我真地以为自己会死
I was scared.
我很怕
Of course you were.
你当然会怕
Thanks.
谢谢
For what?
谢什么？
For not making any jokes.
谢你没嘲笑我
Sure.
当然
Now... open up.
好了 张嘴
- Here.
- 给
Thank you.
谢谢
Just follow this hallway straight down there
顺着走廊直走过去 随意坐
and make yourselves comfortable.
For the good of their family,
(为了家庭考虑）
lynette had made a promise to her husband...
(lynette对丈夫发誓）
and within ten days from the date of purchase,
(在购买后的十天之内）
she intended to keep it.
(她打算留着它）
Oh. That's a fantastic suit.
哦 这件套装太漂亮了
Oh. Thanks.
哦 谢谢
I'm flattered,really.
我很荣幸 真的
I mean,who knew that you cared so much about what i think?
谁知道你会这么在乎我的看法
I don't follow you.
我...不太明白
Well,i make a few innocent comments,
我给了几句无意的评语 你就出去买了一套漂亮的新装
and you go out and buy yourself a gorgeous new suit.
Dance,puppet,dance.
"跳啊木偶来跳舞"
Well,actually,this was already in my closet.
事实上 这个我早就有了 我就是忘了穿了
I just forgot about it.
Forgot? You forgot that you had that suit?
你忘了你有这套衣服?
Good morning. Hi. I'm lynette scavo.
早上好,你好
Now is everyone taken care of in terms of coffee
现在是不是每个人在咖啡方面都很小心
and whatever else they may like? Great.
他们还喜欢什么? 太好了
Well,then let's get started.
那么,我们开始吧
I will show you how kamarov vodka can expand its customer mindshare
我让你们看Kamarov伏特加 是如何在消费者的意识中扩大地位的
while still holding the line on marketing costs.
在保持经营成本的前提下
It's something we here at parcher and murphy
这是我们在烘烤和马铃薯 就像在说劝诱工程
like to call "persuasive engineering."
Lynette...
just hold on one second.
稍等一下
You have a...
咳,你有个...
They put the price tags on the skirts these days,too,
他们现在也在给裙子贴上价格标签
just so you know.
就像你知道的
Look at that,everybody.
大家看那个
Lynette just bought herself a beautiful,brand-new suit.
Lynette刚刚给自己 买了套漂亮的新衣服
Doesn't she look great?
她看上去很棒不是吗?
Go on.
继续
Okay.
好
You may be seated.
可以坐下了
Good to see you back on your feet,mr. Bradley.
很高兴看到你健康的回来了 Bradley先生
Whenever you're ready.
随时只要你准备好了
Thank you,your honor.
谢谢,法官大人
The defense moves to dismiss this case immediately on the grounds that the defendant...
被告方当庭要求撤案 所以被告...
are you all right,mr. Bradley?
你还好吗,Bradley先生?
I'm sorry,your honor. I just can't.
对不起,法官大人 我不能
I just can't.
我不能
Mr. Bradley, do you need a recess?
Bradley先生 你需要休息一下么?
What the hell's going on?
到底发生了什么?
- David,where are you going?
- David,你去哪了?
I'm sorry. I quit.
抱歉. 我不干了
You can't just quit in the middle of a hearing.
你不能在诉讼中撒手不管了
I'd love to get your idiot husband out of jail,
我很想把你的白痴丈夫从监狱里弄出来 但是我真的做不到 抱歉
but i just can't do it. I'm sorry.
- Yeah. Why not?
- 是啊. 为什么不?
Because i'm in love with you.
因为我爱上你了
What?
什么?
The other day in the hospital, i started to feel something.
那天在医院里,我开始有了感觉 我不知道,可能一直都有
I don't know. Maybe it was there all along.
But when i look into your eyes, i know y feel it,too.
而当我看着你的眼睛时 我知道你也有感觉
We belong together.
我们应该在一起
Okay,david,if you don't get back in there right now,
好吧,David,如果你不立刻回去
i will go get a gun and shoot you myself.
我会拿把枪亲手把我干掉
I can't.
我不能
I'm sorry.
对不起
Come in!
进来!
We need to talk.
我们需要谈谈
paul,you... you can't just waltz into people's houses.
Paul,你不能就这样闯到别人家里
Susan,you told me to come in.
Susan,你让我进来的
Well,that's 'cause i assumed you were someone i would let in my house.
恩,那是因为我假定 你是我会让他进来的那个人
What do you want?
你要干什么?
I was looking through my mail, and i found this.
我在看我的信,发现了这个
I was surpriseto discover that you were looking for my son.
我很吃惊地发现 你曾找过我的儿子
You didn't happen to find anything out
你碰巧没找到任何 关于Zach可能在哪的线索,是不是?
about where zach might be, did you?
No. No,i didn't.
不,不,我没有
Sorry i can't help you out.
对不起,我帮不了你
I'm asking because if you remember,
我问你是因为如果你还记得 Zach曾在这个房子里躲过
zach hid here in this house before,
and now i learn that you've been searching for him.
而现在我知道你在找他
Well,he's not here.
他不在这
Well,maybe we should double-check.
恩,也许我们应该仔细地检查一下
But he's not here. I swear.
但他不在这. 我发誓
What are you grabbing for?
你抓的是什么?
A kne.
一把刀
I just want to slice some tomatoes.
我只是想切些西红柿
I don't know how i know this,
我不知道我是怎么知道这个的 但是我...我想他在犹他
but l-i think that he's in utah.
He... he took a bus to bountiful.
他坐车去了Bountiful.
You have family there, right?
你在那有家,不是么?
Okay,i gave him the bus fare.
好吧,我给了他路费
You might want to be careful with that.
你可能想对那事小心点
You seem a little jittery.
你像是有点神经过敏
Look, i know the timing is bad.
看,我知道不是时候
- Pretty bad.
- 非常不是时候
I feel terrible.
我觉得糟透了
How was i supposed to know that he would take a bullet
我怎么知道他会中弹 而且忽然意识到他爱上了我
and suddenly realize he's in love with me?
Okay,look,i know i pushed you into hiring that creep,
好了,看,我知道我逼着你租那个creep
but i promise i will do anything i can to fix this.
我发誓我会尽一切可能解决这件事
All right,go have sex with bradley.
好吧,去和Bradley上床吧
What?
好吧,去和Bradley上床吧 什么?
Well,that's what you want me to say,isn't it?
那就是你想我说的,不是吗?
God,you guys are good. I mean,you set me up perfectly.
天哪,你们真棒 我说,你们帮装地太好了
You think david and i planned this so we could sleep together?
你认为David和我计划好了 这样我们就可以在一起睡了?
Let's see. The guy tells me to my face that he wants
让我想想 那家伙当面告诉我 他想插进你的裤子里
to get into your pants, quits a week before my trial,
在我的审判前辞职一周 而现在你等不及了要做一切来让他回来?
and now you can't wait to do anything to get him back?
Yeah. I'd like to goack to jail now.
- 是. 我现在就想进监狱
How dare you think that of me?
- 你怎么敢那样想我?
I have been nothing but faithful to you!
我除了对你忠诚什么都没做!
Since you've been in here.
自从你进了这里
Save it. I know when i've been outfoxed,
省省吧我知道我什么时候会以计取胜
and please don't pretend that you're doing this for me,
请别装着好像你在为我做这些
'cause i'd rather rot in here.
- 因为我情愿烂在这
And you know what?
你知道吗?
A lesser woman would let you rot in here,
一个差劲的女人会让你烂在这
but i'm not gonna do that.
而我不会那么做
I'm not gonna give you the satisfaction.
我不会让你满足的
So you better start packing up your shanks
所以你最好开始整理你的行李
or whatever you people make in re,
或者你们在这做的任何的事情
because you're coming home with me!
因为你将要跟我一起回家了
I don't have any shanks.
我没有任何行李
Good afternoon. Checking in?
下午好. 开房?
Yes. Reservations in the name of williams... george williams.
是的. 以预定的名字是Williams... George Williams
Let me get your paperwork.
- 让我拿你的文件来
So what do you want to do first?
那么你首先想做什么?
I don't know. I thought maybe we could go antiquing.
我不知道 我想也许我们可以先看些古董
I hear you have some lovely museums nearby.
我听说你们在这附近有些不错的博物馆
Do you have any brochures?
- 你有小册子么? =
Right over there, mrs. Williams.
- 在那里,Williams太太
Oh,uh,she's not my wife.
- 哦,她不是我太太
I'm so sorry.
- 对不起
So i hear they have a terrific farmers' market nearby.
我听说他们在附近有个不错的农业市场 我们应该买些油桃
We shoulpick up some nectarines.
George...
- i can't.
我不能
What?
怎么了?
- I can't stay in a hotel room with you.
- 我不能跟你待在一个宾馆房间
Why not?
为什么不?
Because i am starting to get that rash again.
- 因为我又开始起那个皮疹了
Well,i brought the antihistamines.
我带了抗组胺剂
Oh,please. It's not gonna help.
哦,拜托. 不会有效的 George,很明显,这是受心理影响的
George,clearly, this is psychosomatic.
We need to go home.
我们需要回家
Bree,we just drove three hours to get here.
Bree,我们刚刚开了三个小时车到了这儿
I know,and you have every right to be mad,
我知道,你有很多生气的理由
but,george,i am really starting to itch.
但是,George,我真的开始发痒了
Is there a problem?
- 有什么问题么?
Uh,no,there's no problem. Everything is fine.
- 哦,不,没问题 一切正常
Okay,okay,okay,okay. Uh,uh,
好吧,好吧,好吧,好吧. 恩,恩
i'll get you your own room.
- 我给你另开个房间
George...
no,no,no. We can still have a nice weekend.
不,不,不. 我们仍然会过个愉快的周末
We'll just shift the focus to... antiquing.
我们只要稍稍将重点转移到...古董上
Please. I mean,clearly, you didn't come here to shop.
拜托. 我的意思是 很明显,你不是来这儿购物的
No,i came to spend time with you...
不,我是来和你一起度过的... 度过不用在床上度过的时光
time that does not need to be spent in a bed.
Really? You mean that? You wouldn't mind?
真的? 你这么想? 你不介意?
- No. - You know what,george?
不 你知道,George? 我们会过得很开心
We're gonna have a great time,
你知道,George? 我们会过得很开心
because there's tons of fun stuff we can do
因为有一大堆开心的事可以去做
that doesn't involve sex.
除了性
You betcha.
你说对了
While i take care of this,
我来看着这个 你何不去拿些小册子?
why don't you go get those brochures?
George,you won't believe it.
George,你不会相信的
I just stopped itching.
George,你不会相信的 我不痒了
How about that?
怎么可能?
- Nice suit.
- 不错嘛
Just hear me out.
听我说完
I was gonna take it back, i swear.
- 我正要收回,我发誓
But?
- 但是?
But then i started thinking about it,and you know what?
但是我开始想,你知道么?
I'll be damned if i'm gonna pitch to a roomful of people
如果我向满屋子的人扔过去我将被诅咒 那些只穿ARMANY和Vera Wang的人
who are all wearing armani and vera wang
while i'm standing there with 2-year-old breast milk
在我带着两年的母奶站在那
- crusted on my lapel.
在我的翻领上结了壳
Lynette...
and you know what else?
还有你知道么?
I kicked ass in that meeting because of this suit.
我因为这衣服在会上被整了
Lynette,it is a suit. Why are you so obsessed with it?
Lynette,这只是件衣 你干吗为了它如此困扰?
You can't explain obsession, tom.
你解释不了困扰,Tom
It just... is.
它...就是
No,we are parents.
不,我们是父母 我们承受不了太多的困扰
We can't afford the luxury of obsessions.
See? That's where i think we have been making
看到了吧? 那就是我觉得 我们在哪犯了个严重的,严重的错误
a terrible,terrible mistake.
What is this?
这是什么?
Sometimes we just need to get something that makes us happy.
有时我们只是需要一些东西让我们开心
I know that sounds selfish, but i've been thinking.
我知道这听起来有点自私 但是我一直在想
It might make us better people
这可能会让我我们变成更好的人
and maybe even better parents.
也许更好的父母
No. No,lynette,no. This is wrong.
不,不,Lynette,不. 错了
Carbon... fiber... shafts.
碳素... 光纤... 杆子
I feel like a better parent already.
我已经觉得是好父母了
Oh,yeah.
哦,是啊
So i was talking to one of the bellmen,
我在和其中一个看钟人说话
and he said there's a place not far from here
他说离这不远有个地方 我们能去骑马
where we could go horseback riding.
Doesn't that sound like fun? George?
那听起来不是很有趣么?George?
Wh-what? What? I'm sorry.
恩-- 什么? 什么? 对不起
I was saying i think we should go horseback riding.
我说我在想我们可以去骑马
Oh,sure. That'd be great.
哦,当然. 那很好
- What's wrong?
- 怎么了?
Nothing.
没什么
L-i just don't think that we should risk
我-- 我只是认为我们不该冒险 你再一次起皮疹
you getting another rash.
We,i'm not gonna get another rash just by holding your hand.
我不会就因为拉着你的手而再起皮疹
You never know.
你可不知道
Oh. Well,okay.
哦. 好吧,好
Hey,uh,i brought those antihistamines with me.
嗨,恩,我随身带了这些药
Maybe you should take a couple, just to see if it works.
也许你应该试两片 看看它有没有效
Oh,i'm drinking wine.
哦,我在喝酒
I don'think you're supposed to mix pills with alcohol.
我认为不该将药片和酒精混在一起
That's for people who are...
那是为了那些...
who are about to use heavy machinery.
要干重活的人
You don't plan on operating a forklift tonight,do you?
你今晚又不准备开升降机,不是么?
Well,you're the pharmacist.
你是药剂师
If you think it's okay...
如果你觉得可以...
i do.
是的
George,i can't feel my legs.
George,我都感觉不到我的腿了
I know,sweetheart. Don't you worry.
我知道,亲爱的 你不要担心
I'm gonna take you to your room,
我带你回房间 然后我会把你放到床上
and then we're gonna get you into bed.
Is she going to be okay?
她会没事么?
Yeah,she's just had a little too much wine.
是的,她只是喝多了点
i don't think it was the wine,george.
我想可能不是酒的原因,George
I think it was the antihistamines.
我想是因为药
she doesn't know what she's... we're good,thank you.
她不知道她在... 我们没事,谢谢
No,no,no,no,no.
不,不,不,不,不
I'll get those. You just relax.
我来. 你只要放松
I love you very much,bree. You know that,right?
我非常的爱你,Bree.你知道,对吧?
i know.
我知道
And i want
我想要
more than anything
比什么都多的
for you to love me back.
你对我的爱
Do you understand what i'm saying?
你明白我在说什么吗?
Bree?
Hey there.
嗨
How you feeling?
你觉得怎么样?
Oh,okay.
哦,没事了
Have you been sitting there all this time?
你一直都坐在那儿么?
I wanted to make sure you were okay,
我想知道你没事
so i stayed and watched you sleep.
所以我待在这看你睡觉
Did i do anything embarrassing? Sometimes i snore.
我做了什么难为情的事吗? 有时我大鼾
No. No, you slept like an angel.
不,不,你睡得像个天使
In fact,you were so beautiful and peaceful,
事实上,你是那么的美丽和安静
i actually started to feel guilty.
我开始觉得内疚了
Guilty?
内疚?
Um,well,you know,
恩,你知道
'cause i told you take those pills.
因为我给了你那些药
That chair looks so uncomfortable.
那椅子看上去是那么的不舒服 你为什么不睡在我的旁边
Why didn't you sleep next to me?
Well,you made it pretty clear
恩,你说的很清楚了 你不想让我上你的床
that you don't want me in your bed.
George.
I know what you want from me,
我知道你想从我这得到什么
and i thought i wanted the same thing,
我觉得我也想要同样的东西
but i keep getting those rashes because...
但是我不断起皮疹因为...
i still feel married.
我仍然觉得我已经结婚了
Makes sense,i guess.
可以理解,我想
Can't you just be patient?
你能不能稍微有点耐心?
Can't you wait just a little bit longer?
你能不能稍微多等一等?
I've already waited my whole life for you,
我已经想要为你付出我的一生了
and i can wait a little more.
我可以再多等一段时间
But let's be honest.
但是让我们坦诚点
There's no guarantee that you'll ever be ready.
没有保证你会一直准备着
There's only so much rejection i can take.
我所能承受的拒绝只有这么多了
So...
所以...
i'll do my best,
我会全力以赴
but... don't be surprised
但是... 不要感到惊讶 如果有些天某一天你醒来然后...
if one of these days you wake up and...
i'm not here.
我不在这了
Well,i should get back to my room,
我该回房 试着睡会觉了 古董店十点开门
try to get a little sleep.
The antique stores open at 10.
我该回房 试着睡会觉了 古董店十点开门
George,wait.
George,等等
Please don't go.
请别走
Stay here with me.
跟我一起待在这儿
But what if you get another rash?
但是如果你的皮疹又起了怎么办?
Well,i'll just... have to get over it,won't i?
恩,那我就要克服它,不是么?
Gabrielle?
I got your call...
我被雇佣了...
Does this mean what i think it means?
这是不是意味着我想它表示的意思?
There are some ground rules first.
首先有一些条件
I'm not leaving my husband.
我不会离开我丈夫的
Carlos is looking at spending eight years in jail
Carlos 将在监狱里待上八年 因为我对园丁的判断失误
because of my lapse of judgment with the gardener.
I can't let him rot in there. I'd be filled with guilt.
我不能让他烂在这 我会满心内疚的
You could get him out and then divorce him.
你能把他从这弄出去然后和他离婚
Not an option. I'm catholic,hence the guilt.
这不是个选择 我是天主教徒,因此我会内疚
So what are our options?
那么我们的选择是什么?
This,us,stolen moments,
恩,我们,偷着找时间见面 只要我们可以
seeing each other whenever we n.
Carlos never needs to know.
Carlos 永远不用知道
No.
不
I thought this was what you wanted.
我以为这就是你想想要的
I want all of you.
我要你的全部
All or nothing.
全部还是或是什么都没有
Then it's nothing.
那么就是什么都没有
So you won't get a divorce, but you'll have an affair?
那么你不会离婚 但是你会有风流韵事?
I said i was catholic, not a fanatic.
我说过我是天主教徒 不是盲信徒
You know,david, you could tell me to stop.
你知道,David 你可以让我停下来了
Just tell me to stop, and i will,
让我停下来,我会的
or you can have me right now...
或者你现在就可以拥有我...
on my terms.
在我的条件上
All right.
好吧
Ow! What are you doing?
哦! 你在做什么?
Making my point.
表明我的意思
- You don't love me.
- 你不爱我
Aah! Yes,i do.
不,我爱
No. You just agreed to an affair...
不. 你刚刚同意了一桩风流韵事...
a cheap,illicit affair with the woman you"love."
一个廉价的,违法的韵事 跟一个你"爱" 的女人
Carlos would never share me.
Carlos 永远不会分享我的
He's looking at eight years in prison
他将在监狱里待上八年
because the mere thought of it sent him into a violent rage.
因为一点点这样的想法就让他暴怒
That is love.
那是爱
This is... this is just lust, mixed with posttraumatic stress.
这是...这只是性欲 混合着外伤的压力
I will see you in court tomorrow at 10 a.m.
明天上午10点法庭上见
And don't be late,
别迟到 不然我会因性骚扰将你逐出法庭
or else i'll have you disbarred for sexual harassment.
i'd take it easy with that snail poison.
我将慢慢对付那些蜗牛毒药的
It's hell on your agapanthus.
这是你的爱情花上天敌
Thanks. I'll keep that in mind.
谢谢. 我会记在心里的
Is that why you stopped by...
这就是你拜访的原因吗...
share a few gardening tips?
分享一个新的园艺技巧?
Nobody wants you here,paul, especially me.
没有人想让你在这,Paul,特别是我
I'm just a father looking for his son.
我只是个在寻找儿子的父亲
Oh,i know what you are.
哦,我知道你是什么
First,your girlfriend tries to run me off
首先,你的女朋友设法想让我走掉
with some crazy story about sending zach to utah.
用一些疯狂的关于将Zach送到犹他的故事
Now you're he trying to scare me away.
现在你又想把我吓跑
So much for "love thy neighbor."
对于"爱你的邻居" 已经足够了
Anyway,thanks for the advice.
无论如何,谢谢你的建议
About my agapanthus,i mean.
关于我的爱情花,我说
I'll make sure i send you some.
我保证会送你一点
What did susan tell you?
Susan跟你说了什么?
You look beautiful.
你看起来美极了
Oh,you should really consider wearing this
当你嫁给Mike时 你真的应该考虑穿这个
when you marry mike.
We could make it a family tradition.
我可以将它变成一个家庭传统
Why don't we both stop getting divorced?
我们俩为什么不都停止离婚? 那将是个不错的家庭传统
That would be a nice family tradition.
I need to ask you something important.
我要问你一些重要的事
Oh,my god!
哦,我的天哪!
Aah! This is it!
啊! 就是这个!
Oh! Let me get my camera.
- 哦! 让我拿我的相机来
Oh,no,mom,stop!
哦,不,妈妈,停下!
What is it?
怎么了?
Did you give zach money to go to utah?
你是不是给了Zach去犹他的钱?
What?
什么?
Yes or no.
是还是不是？
He was talking so much about julie.
他说了太多关于Julie的事
I tried to get him to come home with me...
我试着让他跟我一起回家...
i mean,to... to you,
我是说,回...回你那
but he just kept going on and on about her,
但是他只是不听地在说她 然后我害怕了
and i got scared.
Yes or no.
是还是不是
Yes.
是
Mike. Mike,i didn't do it to hurt you.
Mike. Mike,我这样做不是想伤害你
You've gotta believe me. L...
你要相信我. 我...
i should have told you right away. I know that.
我应该立刻告诉你. 我知道
But you know now, so can we please talk about it? (mike) no.
但是你现在知道了 所以请让我们谈谈这个可以吗?
Mike,stop.
Mike,停下
Susan,you said you wanted to help me,and i believed you.
Susan,你说过你想帮我 而我相信了你
That's it. We're done.
就这样,我们完了
No...
不...
No,no,no,no!
不,不,不,不!
I screwed up,okay?!
我从头再来,好吗?!
I want to fix it! Please let me fix it!
我想处理它! 请让我来处理它!
Tell me how to fix it!
告诉我你怎么处理它!
mike... i love you.
Mike... 我爱你
Please,no,please.
拜托,不,求你了
No,mike! Mike,please!
不,Mike! Mike,求你了!
Come back!
回来!
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=- Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园论坛 http://www.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
Sync:YTET-fisherchen -=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
-=COSL-YTET小组工作室=- 听译: 七宝 翻译: 七宝 starry 校对: Uuip 时间轴: fisherchen
Yes,every little girl dreams of a big white wedding.
(是的,每个小女孩都梦想 在盛大的婚礼穿着白色的婚纱)
But some dreams
(但是有的梦想)
just don't come true.
(就是不能实现)
Desperate Housewives
欲乱绝情妻 第二季 第六集
=The End=-
=结束=-